<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    
    <string name="help_topics_text">Tap on a topic below to learn more about it.</string>
    
    <string-array name="help_topics">
        <!-- <item>Setup</item> -->
        <item>Pin</item>
        <item>Keyword</item>
        <item>Commands</item>
        <item>Number Restriction</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <!-- <string name="help_setup">I need to decide what to put here.</string> -->
    
    <string name="help_pin">Your pin is a string of numbers that is used to identify you. You will need to remember it, as it is needed to change settings and use certain commands.\nYour pin must be at least 4 numbers long, with no maximum.\nTo ensure that your pin stays secure, it is only stored in an encrypted format.</string>
    
    <string name="help_keyword">Your keyword is a one-word phrase that is used to address SMSLocator. It is the word that you begin your text message with to instruct SMSLocator to process the message.\nTo ensure that it doesn\'t come up in a normal conversation, you should include letters, numbers, and symbols in your keyword.</string>
    
    <string name="help_restriction">SMSLocator allows you to limit who can interact with it on your phone. You can enter phone numbers of people whom you trust so that only those numbers are allowed. [br][b]It is [u]extremely[/u] important that you will be able to use the devices that the numbers belong to. If you don\'t, you will not be able to talk to SMSLocator as long as the restriction is enabled. Be sure to keep the list up to date![/b][br]Phone numbers must include a + then the country code (ex. +1 for North America). For example, +12345678910</string>
    
    <string name="help_commands">Below is a list of all the commands you can send SMSLocator. Commands marked with (*) are only available with the premium upgrade.</string>
    
    <string-array name="help_commands">
        <item>[Keyword] [pin]</item>
        <item>[Keyword] [pin] lock</item>
        <item>[Keyword] [pin] reset random</item>
        <item>[Keyword] [pin] reset [password]</item>
        <item>[Keyword] [pin] sound</item>
        <item>[Keyword] [pin] ring</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="help_commands_desc">
        <item>Gets the device\'s location</item>
        <item>Locks the device (*)</item>
        <item>Sets the device\'s password to a randomly-generated one (*)</item>
        <item>Sets the device\'s password to the value of [password] (*)</item>
        <item>Sets the device\'s sound mode to ringer (sound on) and disables "Do not disturb" mode on devices running Android M or above (*)</item>
        <item>Makes the device ring (*)</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
